Medbh McGuckian papers, 1964-2006
Emory University
- Printed material, Series 5; Box 48: Folder 4 - Box 71, OP 5-22
  - Writings about Medbh McGuckian, Subseries 5.2; Box 56a: Folder 4 - Box 60; OP 6-15, 29-30
    - Poster for Cuirt 1987, Galway's International Poetry Festival, featuring McGuckian and others (Box OP6)
    - Poster for Poetry Conferences at The Poets' House, June-August 1992, with McGuckian serving on faculty (Box OP7)
    - Poster for reading by McGuckian and others, 23 October 1998 (Box OP8)
    - Poster, Literary Readings in the Curiosity Shop featuring McGuckian and Lionel Shriver, undated (Box OP9)
    - Poster for Poetry and Music Night, featuring McGuckian and others, at the Children's Medical and Research Foundation, undated (Box OP10)
    - Poster for reading by McGuckian and Peter Fallon, Ramelton Georgian Society, undated (Box OP11)
    - Poster for reading by McGuckian, BSU Visiting Writers series, undated (Box OP12)
    - Poster for reading by McGuckian in "The Other Space," undated (Box OP13)
    - Poster for reading by McGuckian and Michael Cody at the Clonakilty Library, undated (Box OP14)
    - Poster for a series of joint readings by McGuckian and Carol Rumens, sponsored by the British Council Poland, undated (Box OP15)
    - Poster for a booksigning at the University Bookshop, Belfast, 1982 (Box OP29)
    - Poster announcing The Irish Times Literature Prize nominees, 1992 (Box OP30)
    - Promotional items (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Promotional items (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Promotional items (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Promotional items (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Promotional items (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Promotional items (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Promotional items (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Other collected printed material, Subseries 5.3; Box 61 - Box 71; OP 16-22
    - Adult Education News, Belfast Institute, September 1994 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - The Agreement: Agreement reached in the multi-party negotiations (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - ALCS News [Authors' Licensing and Collecting Society], May 2005 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - An tUltach, July 1965 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Andersonstown News, 4 April 1998 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Aquarius, 1981/1982 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Aspects Irish Literary Festival Program, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - AWP Newsletter, October 1981 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Ballycastle Writers (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Ballynahinch 1960 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - "Beauty in Light and Darkness," Dennis O'Driscoll [review of Derek Mahon's Selected Poems in Quadrant], June 1993 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Belfast Primary Schools guide (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Belfast Review, Autumn 1983, Winter 1983, Summer 1984, March/April/May 1985, June/July/August 1985, Autumn 1986, Autumn 1987 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Belfast Telegraph, 26 May 1982, 26 January 1984, 30 March 1988 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Bessbrook: An Analysis of its Development since 1759, Thomas Downey [photocopy] (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Biblia, December 1998 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - "Big Poetry," Stephen Schiff [The New Yorker, 14 July 1997] [photocopy] (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - The Blackstaff Press Catalogs, Spring/Summer 1995, Autumn/Winter 2000, Autumn/Winter 2001 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Blast, Winter 1991 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Bloodaxe Books Catalogues, Autumn 1999, Summer & Autumn 2001, undated (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Books and Bookmen, October 1985 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Books Ireland, March 1983, April 1983, October 1988, March 1989, September 1989 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Broadsheet, March 1976, 3 July 1986 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Business Ulster, January 1979 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Carcanet stocklist and catalogue, August 2000-July 2001 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Christ Church College, Oxford University, Honour School of English Language and Literature Pamphlet [photocopy] (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Clé, The Irish Book Publishers Association, Code of Practice (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Co-operation Ireland, Spring 1989 Newsletter and 1988 Annual Report (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - The Crime of Castlereagh (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Crossroads Newsletter, 31 May 1996 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - The Cuirt International Festival of Literature program, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Cumbria, March 1986 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Cyprus Today, July-September 1986 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Daily Mirror, 20 April 1996 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - The Dalesman, March 1991 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Dillon's Book Review, May/June 1997 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Dingle Writing Courses pamphlet, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - "Eliot's Waste Land" by Peter Smark in The Australian Saturday Review, 20 November 1971 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Elliott Bay Booknotes, Spring 1988 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Eolas, Bealtaine 1993 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Faber and Faber book catalogues (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Feasta, Marta 1984 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Feminist Book Fortnight catalogue (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Fiction Magazine, Autumn 1983 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Field Day Theatre program for Chekhov's Three Sisters (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - "A Fire of Stones Curse," Fionnuala Williams (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Flaming Arrows, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Force 10, Spring 1993 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Fortwilliam 50 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - From the Centre [newsletter of the Irish Writers' Centre], Autumn 1995, January 1996, March 1996, November-December 1996, November/December 1998 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - From the Centre [newsletter of the Irish Writers' Centre], [November 1999], April-May 2000, June-August 2000, September-October 2001 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Fusion, October-December 1998, July-September 1999 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - The Galway Advertise r, 15 June 1995 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - The Gazette, The University of Dublin, Trinity College, March 2000 and April 2000 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Gown Literary Supplement, February 1993, Winter 1993/1994 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Graffiti 13, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Grand Opera House Programme for Thomas Kilroy's The Seagull, October 1981 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Graph, October 1986, undated (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - The Guardian, 5 July 1984 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - H-Block: A Selection of Poetry by Republican Prisoners, 1991, photocopy (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - "A Half-Door Near Cluny," Paul Muldoon, Christmas 1997 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Heresay, from the Queen's University Belfast Creative Writing Group and Friends, December 1994 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - History Ireland, Robert Emmet Bicentenary Special Issue, Autumn 2003 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - I am History Now (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - The Independent, 26 May 1998 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Information on Ireland Campaign: Report of the Canadian Fact-Finding Delegation to Northern Ireland, April 8-16, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - The Ireland Funds, Summer 1998 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Ireland Worldwide, July 1992 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - The Irish Garden, January-February 1994 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Irish Literary Collections at Emory Pamphlet (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - The Irish News, 18 September 1982, 29 January 1987, 22 November 1988, 20 February 1990, 3 October 1996, 13 July 1998, 15 July 1998 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - The Irish News and Belfast Morning News, 11 December 1979, 14 May 1980 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Irish Studies at Boston College, Pamphlet (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - The Irish Times, 21 April 1989, 18 May 1991, 28 February 1998, 20 October 1998, undated (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - "An Irishwoman's Diary" [article on Mrs. Cecil Frances Alexander], by Sarah Mac Donald, The Irish Times, 27 November 1995 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - La Jornada, 14 September 1997 (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - "Kevin O'Higgins and the Justice Squad" by Tom Paulin in The Irish Times, undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Kutub, Volume 1, undated (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - An Leitheoir, Spring/Summer 1989 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - The Literary Review, March 1985 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Literature Online Pamphlet (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - The Little Pig, by Adnain [ ? ], dated 15 August 1991 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Literature Quarterly: Literature Events on the South Bank, October-December 1994 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - The London Irish Writer, Spring 1988 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - London Review of Books, 16 April - 6 May 1981, August 1985, 23 October 1986 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - London Review of Books, 5 August 2004 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - lumb bank poetry anthology, June 1985 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Memoirs of Letitia Pilkington [photocopy] (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Moby Dick Catalog, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - "Motion's Poem Fails to Move His Critics" by Dalya Alberge, The Times, 27 December 1999 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Mourne Observer, 15 May 1980 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Munster Literature Centre Newsletter, November/December 1997 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - The Muse (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - "My Own Irish Problem" [article on Seamus Deane] by Helena de Bertodano, The Sunday Telegraph, 5 January 1997 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - New Orleans Review, undated (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - New Prospects Poetry, Spring 1991 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - The New Yorker, 21 June 1982 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - New York Times Magazine, 24 June 1984 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Nil aon tintean (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - North, Winter 1985 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Numbers 2, Spring 1987 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Our Lady of Lourdes Primary School magazine (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Outlines, Winter 1980, [3 copies] (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Outposts, Autumn 1982 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Oxford Poetry, June 1983 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Paintings 1992-1995, John Noel Smith (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Passages North, Summer 1990, Winter 1992 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - "The Past is Orange" [article on Ciaran Carson] by Patricia Deevy, The Sunday Times Culture section, 7 November 1999 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Patrick Kavanagh Centenary Celebrations 1904-2004, booklet (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Poems on Several Occasions [photocopy] (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - "Poet of Sharp Observations with a Keen Outsider's Eye" [review of Peter Porter's Collected Poems] by Robert Nye, undated (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - The Poetry Book Society Bulletin (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Poetry Canada Chronicle, Volume 10, Numbers 2 and 4 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Poetry Canada Review, Summer 1985 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Poetry Canada Review and Chronicle, Summer 1989, Fall 1989, Fall-Winter 1989/1990, Spring 1990 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Poetry Digest, April 1993 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Poetry International, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Poetry News, Summer 1997 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Poetry Now, Autumn 1984 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Poetry Survey, April 1977 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Poetry Toronto, July-August 1984 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - "The Poets of Ireland Lower Their Voices," Jack Holland [photocopy] (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Poster for International Women's Day, 1999 (Box OP16)
    - Poster for Poetry and Painting with Anthony Cronin at the Ulster Museum, 13 November 1994 (Box OP17)
    - Poster for Poetry Reading by Anthony Cronin at the Ulster Museum, 21 April 1994 (Box OP18)
    - Poster for Poetry Reading by Brendan Kennelly at the Ulster Museum, 25 November 1994 (Box OP19)
    - Poster for the Poetry Reading Series at the Winding Stair Bookshop, undated (Box OP20)
    - Poster for the Seventh Annual WERRC Conference Celebrating Irish Women's Writing, May 1999 (Box OP21)
    - Poster for the Women's Worlds Festival, July 1987, Dublin (Box OP22)
    - Prairie Winds (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - The Pushkin Trust Schools' Programme, 2005 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Queen's Letter (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Radio Times, 2-8 February 1980 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Rathmore Grammar School poetry anthology (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Reconciliation and Community: The Future of Peace in Northern Ireland (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Review of Joan McBreen's A Walled Garden in Moylough, by Fred Eckman in Massachusetts Tribune, 9 October 1995 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - The Rialto (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Le Romantisme Anglo-Americaine (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Sask Report (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - "Sean O'Faolain on Frank O'Connor" in The Irish Press, 26 May 1977 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Selected Plays, Cathleen Ni Hoolihan [faxed excerpt] (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - The Shannon, February 1996 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - The Shanty Times, Spring 1995, December 1997, Summer 1999 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - "Sibling Rivalry, Sex and Guns," Laurel Ives [review of Lionel Shriver's A Perfectly Good Family and Susanna Moore's In the Cut] (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Signature (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - The Simmarian (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Sky, Gino, "5 Aces on Christmas Eve" (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Slieve Beagh, Gerry Hull (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - "Soft Cop, Hard Cop," Seamus Deane [review of Terry Eagleton's Heathcliff and the Great Hunger: Studies in Irish Culture in London Review of Books], 19 October 1995 [photocopy] (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Sol Catalog, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Soviet Weekly, 14 February 1987 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - The Spark (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - The Spectator, 27 November 1982 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Spinifex Catalog, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - St. Mary's College, Aims of the College (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Staff-Student News-Report (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - stetProfile, undated (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Stocking Fillers (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Strong Words: Modern Poets on Modern Poetry, ed. W.N. Herbert and Matthew Hollis, selections (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Struga (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Sunday Independent, 23 March 1969, 8 June 1986 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Sunday News, 16 January 1977, 19 July 1981 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - The Sunday Press, 13 March 1983 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - The Sunday Press, 2 October 1994 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - The Sunday Times, 30 June 1991, 8 March 1998 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - The Sunday Times Manual of Creative Photography (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - The Sunday Times Magazine, January 10 1982, January 1 1989 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - The Sunday Tribune, 23 June 1985, 4 December 1988 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Tabacaria, Summer 1998 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - This England (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - The Times, 21 October 1996, 31 March 1999 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - The Times Literary Supplement, 4, 11, and 25 January 1980 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - The Times Literary Supplement, 1 February 1980 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - The Times Literary Supplement, 7, 14, and 21 March 1980 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - The Times Literary Supplement, 23 and 30 May 1980 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - The Times Literary Supplement, 24 October 1986 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Treoir (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Tribune (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - The Tribune Magazine, 3 November 1996 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - "The True Cut of a Cockney" [review of Dickens: Interviews and Recollections, ed. Philip Collins] by Anthony Burgess in [The Observer], 10 January 1982 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - The Tyrone Guthrie Centre at Annaghmakerrig, pamphlet and other materials (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Ulster Tatler, February 1988 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Ulster Youth Theatre program (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - The Unheard Voice: Social Anthropology in Ireland (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - University of Ulster DACE Course Directory (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Uomini e Libri, Nos. 110, 111, 113/114 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Up in Arms: The 1798 Rebellion in Ireland, A Bicentenary Exhibition, Exhibition Guide (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Vision, Summer 1995, Summer 1996, Winter 1996-1997 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - "Voices of Irelands's Women Poets: Mary Dorcey, Paula Meehan, and Eavan Boland," Shane Murphy (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - We Have Kept the Faith, Francis Stuart (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - The White Goddess, Robert Graves [excerpt] (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - The Wide Skirt (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Wilfred Owen Association Newsletter, January 2001 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Women in N. Ireland, Belfast Workers Research Bulletin 5, undated (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Women's News!, December 1996/January 1997, March/April 1997, May/June 1997 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Working the Flow, Jean O'Brien (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - World Poetry Festival Broadsheet, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Zell, Ann, Poems with ALS from Zell to MM (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous other printed material (Box 69, Folder 1-5)
    - Miscellaneous other printed material (Box 70, Folder 1-4)
    - Miscellaneous other printed material (Box 71, Folder 1-4)
- Audio-visual materials, Series 6; Box 72 - Box 73, OP 23-28
  The series contains audio-visual materials including recordings of various interviews and poetry readings and various photographs of McGuckian, her family, and others.
  Organized into two subseries: (6.1) Sound recordings and (6.2) Photographs.
  - Sound recordings, 1979-1994, Subseries 6.1; Box 72 - Box 73: Folder 2
    - "Poetry Competition," 7 December 1979, BBC 2, audio cassette (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - McGuckian on Radio Ulster at CP Downpatrick Festival, 31 July 1980, audio cassette (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Reading at Oklahoma State University, Stillwater, OK, 16 April 1987, audio cassette (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Comhra with McGuckian and Ní Dhomhnaill, 18 December 1992, 3 audio cassettes (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Reading at the University of Arizona, Center for Creative Photography, 17 October 1994, audio cassette (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous McGuckian Recordings, undated, audio cassette (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Readings by Crozier, Ormsby, Lane, and McGuckian, undated, audio cassette (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Subseries 6.2; Box 73: Folders 3-14; OP 23-28
    - Photographs of Medbh McGuckian
    - Medbh McGuckian (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Medbh McGuckian (Box OP23)
    - Medbh McGuckian with family (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Medbh McGuckian with family (Box OP24)
    - Medbh McGuckian with family (Box OP25)
    - Medbh McGuckian with family (Box OP26)
    - Medbh McGuckian with family (Box OP27)
    - Medbh McGuckian with other Irish writers, including Seamus Heaney, Michael Longley, and Paul Muldoon, undated (Box OP28)
    - Medbh McGuckian with others (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Other photographs
    - Carson, Ciaran (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Gallagher, Tess (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - McBreen, Joan (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - McGuckian family (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Muldoon, Paul (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Objects and scenery (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Objects and scenery [from Cathal O Searcaigh] (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Others (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Negatives
    - Negatives (Box 73, Folder 14)
- Unprocessed additions, Series 7; Boxes 74-78
  Unprocessed correspondence is closed to researchers.
  - Writings, Manuscript and typescript (Box 74)
  - Correspondence [RESTRICTED] (Box 75)
  - Correspondence [RESTRICTED] (Box 76)
  - Correspondence [RESTRICTED] (Box 77)
  - Notebooks (Box 78)
Index of Selected Correspondents
ARCHER, NUALA 1986 January 10, 1p w/ envelope 1986 December 1, TLS, 1p 1987 January 12, TLS, 1p 1987 May 5, TLS, 1 p w/ envelope 1990 January 7, ACS 1994 July 21, ACS 1995 January 28, ALS, 1p 1996 February 18, post card undated, ACS undated, ACS
BOLAND, EAVAN undated, TLS, 3pps undated, ALS, 1p undated, ACS
CARSON, CIARAN 1973 November 11, TLS, 1p w/ envelope 1974 June 15, TLS, 2pps 1974 June 23, ACS 1974 June 26, TLS, 1p 1974 July 2, TLS, 2pps w/ envelope 1974 July 11, TLS, 2pps w/ envelope 1974 July 15, TLS, 2pps w/ envelope 1974 July 19, TLS, 1p w/ envelope 1974 July 24, ALS, 2pps w/ envelope [1974], TLS, 2pps [1974], TLS, 1p [1974], TLS, 1p [1974], TLS, 1p 1976 March 23, TL, 1p w/ envelope, w/ poem "St. Ciaran & His Friends" 1976 May 19, TL, 1p w/ envelope 1976 June 3, TL, 1p w/ envelope 1976 August 20, ACS w/ envelope 1976 September 3, ALS, 2pps w/ envelope 1976 September 13, ALS, 2pps w/ poem "An Early Photograph" [1976], TL, 1p [1976], ALS, 1p 1977 March 10, APS 1991 June 3, TLS, 3pps w/ poem "On Not Remembering Some Lines of a Song" 1994 August, TL, 4pps 2004 January 28, email 2004 January 29, email 2004 February 18, email 2004 March 21, ALS to Ciaran Carson from McGuckian, 1p 2004 March 25, email undated, TLS, 3pps undated, ANS undated, TLS, 2pps undated, ALS, 1p undated, ALS, 1p undated, ACS undated, TLS, 2pps undated, TLS, 3pps w/ poem "Wet Leaves" by Frank Ormsby undated, ANS undated, TLS, 1p undated, ALS, 1p undated, TLS to Ciaran Carson from McGuckian, 1p undated, ALS, 1p undated, APS
COLLINS, BILLY 2004 January 28, email 2004 February 23, email 2004 March 15, email
CROSS, DOROTHY 1993 November 17, TLS, 1 p 1994 February 6, ACS
DAWE, GERALD 1982 September 12, ACS 1984 May 14, TLS, 1p 1984 June 7, TLS, 1p 1984 June 18, ALS, 1p 1984 June 21, ALS, 1p 1984 August 8, ALS, 1p 1986 November 11, ACS 1992 September 28, TLS, 1p 1994 January 17, ALS, 1p 1999 October 20, ALS, 1p 1999 October 29, post card 2000 February 24, ALS, 1p w/ envelope Undated, ALS
DEANE, SEAMUS 1992 March 11, TLS, 1p w/ envelope 1996 March 25, TLS, 1p w/ envelope 1999 March 20, TLS, 1p w/ envelope undated, APS
DORGAN, THEO 1990 August 10, ACS 1990 November 27, TLS, 1p w/ envelope 1992 January 28, TLS, 2pps 1992 March 10, ALS, 1p 1992 March 11, TLS, 1p 1993 July 10, TLS, 1p w/ 14pps of poetry and envelope, poems: "The Inquisitor Considers the Daughters of Eve," "The Match Down the Park," "A Neighbor of Ours," "Nine Views of Uzbekhistan," "House Over the Harbour at Ballintoy," "Red Square," "The Prisoners of Lord Lane," "The Geography of Armagh," "Kilmainham Gaol, Dublin, Easter 1991," "The Flaming Door" 1993 September 2, TLS, 1p 1994 December 12, TLS, 2pps w/ envelope w/ additional materials 1995 January 8, ALS, 1p w/ envelope 1995 May 3, TLS, 1p 1995 October 26, 1p 1996 February 29, 2pps w/ envelope 1996 February, 1p 1996 May 1, 1p 1997 July 8, 1p 1997 October 20, 1p 1998 February 12, 1p 1999 March 11, 1p 1999 August 25, 1p 2000 January 17, ALS, 1p undated, 1p undated, 1p
DUFFY, CAROL ANN 1999 June, TLS, 2pps w/ envelope 1999 June 25, post card 2000 January 5, TLS, 1p
DURCAN, PAUL 1987 February 20, ANS 1987 February 27, ACS 1987 March 10, ACS 1987 March 15, ALS, 1p 1987 March 19, ALS, 3pps 1987 March 22, ALS, 3pps w/ envelope 1987 April 4, ALS, 2pps w/ envelope 1987 September 21, ALS, 1p w/ envelope 1988 February 27, ACS undated, ACS undated, ACS
EAGLETON, TERRY 1989 October 7, 1p